[{
  "Name": "Spanish alphabet",
  "Cards": [
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce A in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AH"
  },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce B in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "BAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce C in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce D in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "DAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce E in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce F in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "EFFAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce G in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "HAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce H in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AH-CHAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce I in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "EE"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce J in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "HO-TAH"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce K in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "KAH"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce L in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AY-YAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce M in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AY-MAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce N in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AY-NAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce Ã‘ in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AY-EN-YAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce O in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "OH"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce P in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "PAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce Q in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "KOO"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce R in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AY-RAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce S in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AY-SAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce T in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "TAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce U in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "OO"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce V in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "OO-BAY"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce W in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "DOH-BLAY OO-bay"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce X in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "AY-KEES"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce Y in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "EE-GREE-EH-GAH"
    },
    {
    "Question": "How do you pronounce Z in the Spanish alphabet?",
    "Answer": "SAY-tah"
    }
  ]
}]